READING
COME AND EAT HERE
1.
VANG PUNG SAT IN HIS EMPTY RESTAURANT, FEELING VERY FRUSTRATED.
It had been a very strange morning.
Then by lunchtime they would all be sold.
By now his restaurant ought to be full of people.
But not today!
Why was that?
He thought of his mutton, beef and bacon cooked in the hottest,
finest oil.
His cola was sugary and cold, and his ice cream was made of milk,
cream and delicious fruit.
Nothing could be better," he thought.
Hello, Lao Li," he called.
What was the matter?
Tired of all that fat?
Want to lose weight?
Make yourself thin again!
It was full of people.
The hostess, a very thin lady, came forward.
Welcome," she said.
There were few choices of food and drink on it:
just rice, raw vegetables served in vinegar,
fruit and water.
He could not believe his eyes.
He threw down the menu and hurried outside.
On his way home he thought about his own menu.
Did it make people fat?
Perhaps he should go to the library and find out.
He had better do some research!
They would become tired very quickly.
Perhaps with a discount and a new sign he could win his customers back.
So he wrote: Want to feel fit and energetic?
Come and eat here!
Discounts today!
Our food gives you energy all day!
The competition between the two restaurants was on!